here are the stories were covering this
这里有关于此的故事
week in the category 5 TV news room
一周在 5 类 电视新闻室
kayla is now illegal in Germany the
kayla 现在在德国非法了
founder of Florida marketing firm who
佛罗里达营销公司的创始人
use illicit tactics to send spam email
使用非法策略发送垃圾邮件
has been sent to jail bill gates thinks
已经被送到监狱的盖茨盖茨认为
the government should tax the robot to
政府应该对机器人征税
take the jobs of human workers
接受人类工作的工作
february's critical update to Microsoft
2月对微软的重大更新
Windows has been delayed despite its
尽管如此， Windows仍被推迟
urgency and using google and using
紧迫感和使用谷歌和使用
machine learning Google's Project loon
机器学习Google的Project loon
is moving quickly to bringing Internet
正在迅速采取互联网
services to areas where it was
为其所在地区提供服务
previously unavailable these stories are
以前没有这些故事
coming right up don't go anywhere now
来吧，现在不去任何地方
here's another great way you can support
这是另一种你可以支持的好方法
the shows you love for the category 5 TV
你喜欢5类电视的节目
network by shopping gear best that's
网络购物装备最好的那个
right down cat5 TV / gear best it's an
右下方cat5电视/ 装备最好它是一个
online store for the geek streak in you
在线商店为 你的极客连胜
or the loved ones well of course I mean
当然，我的 意思是亲人
especially your loved ones right because
特别是你的亲人，因为
cat 5 gb / gearbest quite frankly has
猫5 gb / gearbest相当坦率地说
all of the greatest tech gifts that you
你所有最伟大的科技礼物
could ever hope for at rock bottom
可能希望在最低点
prices because that cell phones you bet
价格，因为你打赌手机
you cap five TV / gear vest has a wide
你有五个电视/齿轮背心有一个宽
assortment of unlocked android cell
各种解锁的android手机
phones and tablets global compute
手机和平板电脑全球计算
consumer electronics those like a great
消费电子产品 就像一个伟大的
gift absolutely from high-tech watches
绝对来自高科技手表的礼物
to action cameras headphones even
到行动相机耳机甚至
virtual reality headsets cat five dot TV
虚拟现实耳机猫五点电视
/ gearbest has you covered they
/ gearbest 让你覆盖他们
literally have it all Jeff literally
从字面上看，这真是杰夫
really it's like a super store right
真的，这就像超级商店吧
from the comfort of your own share add
从您自己的舒适分享添加
your computer through the interweb
你的电脑通过互联网
yeah I there's no way they have it all
是的，我没有办法让他们拥有一切
through it's just a bunch of random
通过它只是 一堆随机
electronic test me what about clothes
电子测试我的衣服怎么样
yep both men and women fashionable
是的男人和女人时髦
apparel at rock bottom SuperDuper prices
服装在岩石底部SuperDuper价格
kinda like this well look at this coat
有点像这样看看这件外套
what do you think it's a slimming mock
你怎么认为这是一个减肥模拟
leather jacket I love it it's available
皮夹克我喜欢它可用
for less than thirty dollars plus free
少于三十美元加免费
shipping a cat5 da TV / gearbest yeah
运送cat5 da TV / gearbest是的
all right you kind of got me there Wow
好吧，你有点让我在那里哇
any other questions for me Jeff now that
现在任何其他问题杰夫杰夫
winter is past flying season do they
冬天是过去的飞行季节吗？
have any good deals and save your own
有任何好的交易，保存自己的
cups oh my goodness well check this out
杯子哦，天哪， 好好看看这个
dude they have everything check out over
老兄他们有一切都检查过来
500 various groans and not only that
500种不同的呻吟，不仅如此
they're available mark down by about
他们可以用约标记
thirty two up to sixty-three percent off
三十二，高达百分之六十三折
the regular price love it what's website
正常价格喜欢它的网站
again while you're going to find
你会发现的
gearbest on our partners pages for any
我们的合作伙伴页面上的任何设备
of your favorite category five TV shows
您最喜欢的 五类电视节目
like new every day category five
像每天新的五类
technology TV the pixel shadow but of
技术电视的像素阴影但是
course if you want to shop absolutely
当然，如果你想绝对购物
right now and you want to go straight to
现在，你想直接去
the site all you have to do is visit
该网站所有你要做的就是访问
cat5 TV / gearbest that's easy catch
cat5 电视/ gearbest很容易捕获
five dot TV / gear back that's right
五点电视/装备是正确的
happy shopping I'm Sasha through madison
快乐购物我是萨莎通过麦迪逊
here are the top stories for the week of
这是本周的热门故事
februari 22nd 2017 remember the kala
februari 2017年2月22日记得卡拉
doll we reported on during episode 481
我们在第481集中报道过的娃娃
well it's now illegal in Germany to sell
那么在德国出售它现在是非法的
the talking doll and that's just the
说话的娃娃，这只是
beginning a German government watchdog
开始了德国政府监管机构
has ordered parents to destroy the
已下令父母摧毁了
internet connected doll for fear it
互联网连接的玩偶因为害怕它
could be used as a surveillance device
可以用作监视设备
according to a report from the BBC News
根据来自BBC 新闻 的报告
the German Federal Network agency said
德国联邦网络机构说
the doll which contained a microphone
包含麦克风的娃娃
and speaker was equivalent to a
和扬声器相当于一个
concealed transmitting device and
隐藏的发射装置和
therefore prohibited under German
因此德国禁止
telecom law in dissent in December last
电信法在12月份持不同意见
year privacy advocates said that the toy
年隐私权拥护者称玩具
recorded kids conversations without
没有记录孩子的谈话
proper consent
适当的同意
violating the children's online privacy
侵犯了孩子的在线隐私
protection act thank goodness for them
保护法谢天谢地
the Act themselves yeah kayla uses a
法案本身是啊凯拉使用了
microphone to listen to questions
麦克风听取问题
sending this audio over Wi-Fi to a third
通过Wi-Fi将此音频发送到第三个
party company that converts it to text
派对公司将其转换为文本
this is then used to search the internet
这用于搜索互联网
allowing the adult answer basic
允许成人回答基本
questions like what's a baby kangaroo
像小袋鼠这样的问题
called as well as play games in addition
此外还有游戏和游戏
to privacy concerns over data collection
关于数据收集的隐私问题
security researchers found that Kayla
安全研究人员发现凯拉
can easily be hacked the dolls in
很容易被黑客入侵
secured Bluetooth connection can be
安全的蓝牙连接即可
compromised letting a third-party record
妥协让第三方记录
audio via the toy or even speak to
通过玩具的音频，甚至说话
children using its voice mmm so bad the
孩子们用它的声音嗯这么糟糕了
Electronic Privacy Information Center
电子隐私信息中心
has said that toys like this subject
曾经说过像这样的玩具主题
young children to ongoing surveillance
幼儿要持续监视
without any meaningful data protection
没有任何有意义的数据保护
standards one researcher pointed out
标准一位研究人员指出
that the doll was accessible from up to
从最多可以访问玩偶
33 feet away even through walls using a
距离墙壁33英尺远
bluetooth-enabled device there is
支持蓝牙的设备
nothing scarier than the Ahmet the
没有比艾哈迈德更可怕了
imagined threat not even imagine that
想象中的威胁，甚至无法想象，
the real threat that your children could
你的孩子可能面临的真正威胁
be like talked to from somebody this all
好像从这个人那里谈过这一切
has its own voice I almost think like a
有自己的声音，我几乎认为是一个
Chucky or something out of yeah let's
Chucky或者是什么， 是的，让我们
play you know it's going to sell at
玩你知道 它会卖掉
least is your life at least this with
至少你的生活至少是这样的
dolls voice and not like the voice of
娃娃的声音和不喜欢的声音
Lucifer yeah because that was you know
路西法耶，因为那是你知道的
sweetened innocent or children they'd
他们是 无辜的 或 无辜的 孩子
probably like offer up any amount of
可能喜欢提供任何数量的
information to a doll that was talking
给正在谈话的玩偶的信息
to it that yeah very point yeah I got
对它说， 是的，我得到了
your parents home do you have a dog
你的父母回家你有一只狗吗？
things like that right so it can be very
像这样的事情， 所以它可以非常
scary I want you to watch the code that
可怕的我要你看代码
mummy puts into the you know the pink
木乃伊放入你知道的粉红色
our thing there's four members you
我们这里有四个成员你
remember them and tell them to me later
记得他们，然后告诉他们
you know oh I hope you want stuff like
你知道哦，我希望你 想要的东西
that not well at least there is laws
至少没有法律
against it at least this one has been
反对它，至少这一个
caught I mean like when I was a kid I
抓住我的意思就像我小时候一样
had bingo the bear and there was Teddy
有宾果熊和泰迪
Ruxpin and that girl yeah and bingo was
Ruxpin 和那个女孩耶和宾果是
like the knockoff oh it was like the you
像淘汰赛哦，它就像你
know and i loved it i had that thing for
知道，我喜欢它，我有那个东西
years me being the little hacker that i
几年我是小黑客， 我
was I
是我
built an AC converter for it and made it
为它制造了一个AC转换器并制造它
so I could plug it into the wall because
所以我可以 将它插入墙上，因为
I was tired of the batteries getting run
我厌倦了电池 运转
out here I am like the size of my
在这里，我就像我的大小
youngest is during the wall everywhere
最小的是到处都是墙
with you and you're okay yeah compatible
和你在一起你很好，是的兼容
long but they were so benign I'm so
很长，但他们是如此温和，我是如此
innocent because like you'd squeeze his
无辜的，因为就像你挤他的一样
mouth and he would say pre-recorded
嘴巴，他会说预先记录
saying well it's what every networks so
说得好，这就是每个网络都是如此
right that was it there was no Wi-Fi
没错，就是没有Wi-Fi
there was no bleach exactly no
没有漂白剂
artificial intelligence or even you know
人工智能，甚至你知道
text to speech was like dr. Speights
文本到语音就像博士。斯贝茨
though back then it was not anywhere
虽然当时它不是在任何地方
near where we are now so yes they can
我们现在所在的地方附近也是如此
type in things that's a scary thing so
输入那些可怕的东西
i'm waiting for all those videos to hit
我正在等待所有这些视频
YouTube of people blowing up their Kayla
YouTube上的人们炸毁了他们的 Kayla
dolls no that'd be awesome slow mo guys
娃娃没有那个令人敬畏的慢动作
fantastic Wow okay a marketer who used
太棒了哇好吧营销人员使用过
stolen email accounts to collect more
被盗的电子邮件帐户收集更多
than a million dollars by spamming
通过垃圾邮件发送超过一百万美元
people has been sent to prison for four
人们被送进了四个监狱
years Timothy Livingston who's 31 was
多年来， 蒂莫西·利文斯顿是31岁
handed the 48 months term after he
在他之后交出了48个月的任期
pleaded guilty kit two counts of
认罪两件罪名
conspiracy to commit fraud in connection
串谋欺诈行为
with computers and access devices
与计算机和访问设备
with electronic mail and aggravated
用电子邮件加重
identity theft the sentence was handed
身份被盗被判刑
out on Thursday by Judge William J
周四由威廉J法官出庭
martini in the New Jersey district court
马丁尼在新泽西 地区法院
where Livingston pled guilty to the
利文斯顿认罪的地方
charges last year based in Boca Raton
去年在博卡拉顿收费
Livingston ran and operated a marketing
利文斯顿经营和营销
company called a whole lot of nothin LLC
公司叫了很多nothin LLC
which specializes in sending out bulk
专门发送批量
emails for clients the US Department of
美国电信部客户的电子邮件
Justice said Livingston's clients
Justice说利文斯顿的客户
included legitimate businesses such as
包括合法的企业，如
insurance companies that wish to send
希望 发送的保险公司
bulk emails to advertise their
批量电子邮件来宣传他们的
businesses as was as well as illegal
企业既是非法的 ，也是非法的
entities such as online pharmacies that
在线药店等实体
sold narcotics without prescriptions
没有处方就卖毒品
what the clients did not know or chose
客户不知道或选择的是什么
not to ask was how Livingston was able
不要问利文斯顿是如何做到的
to send out so many emails the marketer
向营销人员发送这么多电子邮件
had an arsenal of botnet controlled
有一个僵尸网络控制的武器库
accounts and compromised servers who use
帐户和使用的受感染服务器
to help send out the spam runs without
帮助发送垃圾邮件运行没有
being identified or detected by spam
被垃圾邮件识别或检测到
filters he would then collect the
他会收集过滤器
commission every time one of his junk
每次 他的一个垃圾 委托
mail messages was converted to a sale
邮件已转换为销售
Livingston's co-defendant Tomasz shemal
利文斯顿的共同被告Tomasz shemal
res of new jersey also admitted writing
新泽西的 res 也承认写作
the malware used to infect and control
用于感染和控制的恶意软件
the botnets by the time of ington was
ington时代的僵尸网络是
finally caught it is estimated his
终于抓到了估计他的
spamming network was able to rack up
垃圾邮件网络能够成功
around 1.35 million dollars in
约135万美元
ill-gotten gains he will have to forfeit
他将不得不放弃不义之财
all of that as part of his plea deal oh
所有这些都是他认罪协议的一部分哦
well I would hold yeah I say this this
好吧， 我会坚持，是的，我这样说
is one of those scary people are smart
是那些可怕的聪明人之一
and businesslike appeared like a
和事务似乎是一个
legitimate business except that it was
合法的业务，除了 它
called all about nothing but yes but it
什么都没有，只有是， 但它
appears legitimate and I met people
看似合法， 我遇到了人
kidding name yeah hey you know what
开玩笑的名字呀嘿你知道吗
flashy signs gets them every time right
华而不实的迹象每次都得到它们
billionaire emails and obviously it had
亿万富翁的电子邮件，显然它有
enough a lure that people who were
足够诱惑那些人
legitimate businesses and also
合法的企业也
illegitimately this is felt equally
非法地认为这是平等的
comfortable using him right yeah I don't
对他说得好，我没有
know okay Bill Gates the co-founder of
知道 好吧比尔盖茨的联合创始人
Microsoft and the world's richest man
微软和全球首富
said in an interview friday that robots
在星期五的一次采访中说机器人
that steals human jobs should pay their
窃取人类工作应该支付他们的工资
fair share of taxes right now the human
公平分享税收现在是人类
worker who does say fifty thousand
说五万的工人
dollars worth of work in a factory that
在一家工厂工作的美元
income attack then you get income tax
收入攻击然后你获得所得税
Social Security tax and all of those
社会保障税和所有这些
things he said if a robot comes in to do
他说如果一个机器人进来做的话
the same thing you'd think that we tax
同样的事情，你会认为我们征税
the robot at a similar level well mmm
机器人处于类似的水平
gates made the remark during an
盖茨在一段时间里发表了这番话
interview with quartz he said robot
采访石英他说机器人
taxes could help fund projects like
税收可以帮助资助项目
caring for the elderly or working with
照顾老人或与之合作
children in school quartz reported that
孩子们在学校石英报道说
European Union lawmakers considered a
欧盟立法者考虑过
proposal to tax robots in the past and
过去和过去对机器人征税的建议
the law was rejected well I understand
我明白 ， 法律被拒绝了
well I would think that by taxing the
好吧，我会认为通过征税
robots you'd be taxing the people who
机器人你会对那些人征税
own the robots but at the same time
拥有机器人，但同时
where do you draw the line though
你在哪里画线
because it's like are you going to tax
因为它就像你要征税一样
like an auto pilot over there
就像那边的自动驾驶员
plain are you can attack Siri or aren't
平原你可以攻击Siri或不是
only going to tat like tag certain
只是像标签一样
industries or like I was like other ones
行业或像我一样喜欢其他行业
that replaced the humans but until white
它取代了人类但直到白色
point like yeah taxing the ATM could it
点赞，是的，可以为ATM征税
be thinking humanoid so like anything
像任何人一样思考人形
like I can I can think of like in a car
就像我能在车里想到的那样
plant for example like the robots
例如像机器人一样的工厂
putting on doors and stuff sure yeah
穿上门，东西肯定是的
because like you know the kado industry
因为你知道 kado行业
is a big thing right now and politics
现在和政治是一件大事
and all that stuff but it's like you
所有的东西，但它就像你
gauge it we're going out on the line
衡量一下，我们要走出去了
like that in how you engage it how do
就像你如何参与其中一样
you say X number of jobs have been
你说X的工作数量已经有了
replaced when especially when you think
特别是在你想的时候更换
about the transition of industry and how
关于行业的转型和如何
industry is going to make the transition
行业将会使过渡
to robotics as operators and Anatomy
作为操作员和解剖学的机器人学
facturers and well these jobs that are
这些工作就是这样的工作者
being created for these robots never
永远不会为这些机器人创建
existed for humans because it didn't
存在于人类，因为它没有
exist yet right i mean there's the job
存在但是我的意思是有工作
of making the robots and there's the job
制造机器人并且有工作
of the maintenance of the robot yeah
维修机器人是的
right there's jobs at the robots create
就在那里，机器人的工作创造了
not only just take away sure but i like
不仅仅是带走肯定，但 我喜欢
i can't imagine what you're what they're
我无法想象你是什么样的人
saying is that the taxes would then have
说是税收会有
to be paid by the owners of the robots
由机器人的所有者支付
yeah right so then the owner of your
是的，那么你的主人
robot is paying there's a good idea but
机器人付钱有一个好主意但是
yeah it's a neat idea as far as
是的，这是一个很好的想法
personalized you i don't but it seems
个性化你 我 不会，但似乎
like a really slippery slope as again it
就像一个非常滑的斜坡一样
says you have to define how you want to
说你必须定义你想要的方式
do it like again are you going to tax
再次这样做你要征税吗？
court anna for being on your computer
法庭安娜在你的电脑上
for helping us scheduling welcome
帮助我们安排欢迎
cocaina i don't want that excited
cocaina 我不想那么兴奋
anything microsoft but yeah i'll go see
什么微软，但是，我会去 看看
your hacks on that guy I understand
你理解那个人的黑客行为
taxis are fairly unavoidable but I got
出租车是相当不可避免的，但我得到了
you like being a robot should get you a
你喜欢做一个机器人应该得到你
pass on that or are you too you too
传递那个，或者你也是
though you save so many people and
虽然你节省了这么多人和
you're going to tax r2d2 and c3po now
你现在要对r2d2和c3po征税
right I mean like they've helped save
对， 我的意思是他们帮助拯救了
the galaxy a few dozen times and now
银河十几次现在
we're going to be charging tax right
我们要收税
same with data from star trek right and
与星际迷航中的数据相同
are they taxing okay so they're saying
他们在说他们的税收是否正常？
that as a robot that's replaced a human
那个机器人取代了人类
that was making fifty thousand dollars a
那是五万美元一个
year but then if the robots running 24
一年，但如果机器人运行24
hours a day whereas if you
一天一小时，如果你
when was running exactly 10 hours a day
什么时候每天运行10个小时
well now are they all the segments in
现在他们是所有细分市场
Slate that and I are more attacks it
我和Slate更加攻击它
does that come from yeah but I guess
那是不是来自 耶，我想
they're manufacturing the same amount or
他们制造相同数量或
more stuff so but you mentioned data but
更多的东西，但你提到数据，但
data in the show did kind of operate
在数据显示没有那种操作
like a human but we're nowhere near that
就像一个人，但我们远不及那个
our jobs are not being going to be
我们的工作不会成为现实
replaced by data like androids knock on
取而代之的是像机器人这样的数据
wood I mean Bill Gates famously say we
木头我的意思是比尔盖茨有名的说我们
only need 640k right a high memory but
只需要640k 右高内存但是
you know there's oh really bound to be
你知道哦，真的很有必要
wrong eventually but ya know Gatewood
最终错了，但你知道Gatewood
might be wrong on this one ya know bill
这个知道 账单可能有问题
game his company Microsoft yeah okay so
游戏，他的公司微软是啊好吧，
this is this is something that he's
这就是他的意思
wrong about there we go you know one of
错误的我们去你知道其中一个
the founders but yeah he's not really in
创始人，但是他不是真的
charge anymore that's all it offers for
再收费就是它所提供的一切
me Microsoft has delayed the release of
我微软推迟了发布
security update that would have fixed
可以修复的安全更新
the vulnerability cyber thieves are
漏洞网络窃贼是
known to be exploiting the fix would be
已知被剥削的解决将 是
released as part of Microsoft's regular
作为微软常规的一部分发布
monthly security update for its Windows
其Windows的每月安全更新
software in a blog it said a last minute
博客中的软件最后一分钟说
issue had got in the way of the updates
问题妨碍了更新
being sent out as usual the delay is
像往常一样被送出延迟是
thought to be related to changes
被认为与变化有关
Microsoft was due to make to be the way
微软应该成为这样的道路
updates were delivered the februari
februari提供了更新
update was scheduled to include a patch
更新计划包括一个补丁
for a problem with a part of Windows
对于Windows的一部分问题
that handles particular types of file
处理特定类型的文件
transfers the bug was first reported to
首次报告错误的转移
Microsoft in September and code to
微软在9月和代码
exploit it is believed to be available
利用它被认为是可用的
to malicious hackers the flaw is present
对 恶意黑客来说，这个漏洞存在
in most versions of Windows and could
在大多数Windows版本中都可以
leave users open to attacks let hackers
让用户开放攻击让黑客入侵
crash vulnerable machines Microsoft has
崩溃易受攻击的机器微软
already delayed releasing the file
已经推迟发布文件
transfer fix because it wanted to
转移修复因为它想要
include it with other updates for the
包含它与其他更新
same Windows subsystem that it
它与Windows子系统相同
previously planned for februari februari
以前计划为februari februari
was also when Microsoft was due to break
当微软即将破产时也是如此
its security fixes into two one for
它的安全性修复为两个
windows and the other first browsers
Windows和其他第一批浏览器
getting the separation and testing
获得分离和测试
systems to work reliably is believed to
据信，系统可靠地工作
have caused to delay no date has been
导致延迟没有约会
given for when the delayed update will
给予延迟更新的时间
be
是
delivered the fat just mean that people
传递脂肪只是意味着 人
are still free to go ahead and exploit
仍然可以继续开发利用
right yeah technically yeah right yeah
对，是的，技术上是的，是的，是的
if they're if it's active in the wild
如果他们是在野外活跃的话
then I guess the fix is endowed thing
然后我想修复是赋予的东西
right never really net they've got to do
从来没有真正的网络，他们必须做
it soon though but one commenter was
很快， 但是一位评论者却是
like well it's typical Microsoft style
喜欢这是典型的微软风格
once they know a bug is out in the wild
一旦他们知道野外就有虫子了
they wait two years and then they patch
他们等了两年， 然后 他们补丁
it that's right hmm okay written it
这是正确的嗯好吧写的
better news reached researchers at
研究人员获得了更好的消息
Google say that they are years closer to
谷歌表示，他们距离更近了几年
rolling out a network of huge balloons
推出一个巨大的气球网络
to provide connectivity to rural areas
提供与农村地区的连接
the project loon team part of the
项目懒人团队的一部分
company's X research lab said that it
公司的X研究实验室说它
was now able to use machine learning to
现在能够使用机器学习了
predict weather systems it means the
预测天气系统就意味着
firm has far greater control over where
公司对哪里有更大的控制权
its balloons go making it possible to
它的气球让它成为可能
focus on a specific region rather than
专注于特定区域而不是
circumnavigating the globe clustering a
环游地球聚集a
small number of balloons greatly reduces
少量气球大大减少
the cost of the idea Google's captain of
这个想法的成本谷歌的队长
moon shots Astro teller told reporters
月球拍摄阿斯特罗出纳员告诉记者
he says we can now run an experiment and
他说我们现在可以进行实验了
try to give service in a particular
试着给某个特定的服务
place in the world with 10 20 or 30
10 20或30世界的地方
balloons he said rather than the
他说的气球而不是气球
hundreds needed previously oh that's
以前需要数百个哦
incredible real users will be able to
令人难以置信的真实用户将能够
use the system in the coming months he
他将在未来几个月内使用该系统
added but he did not specify where the
补充但他没有说明在哪里
initial rollout would take place finally
最初的推出将会进行
a little bright spot in the newsroom
新闻编辑室有点亮点
that is great so could activity like in
这很棒，所以活动就像在
places that just would never otherwise
那些绝不会的地方
do you think of like third world
你觉得像 第三世界吗？
countries and take it like that that's
国家，并把它当作那样
where our mind immediately goes at the
在那里我们的脑海中会立即转到在
same time though is that like being a
同时虽然就像是一个
pilot myself I asked at what altitude
自己飞行员我问到了什么高度
like are these like very a high of 11
喜欢这些非常高的11
150 thousand feet above airliners
飞机上方15万英尺
because if there are 20,000 feet that's
因为如果有20,000英尺的话
below airliners it's like I don't want
在飞机下面，它就像我不想要的那样
to be flying around and say no I'm giant
飞来飞去， 说不，我是 巨人
it's going to be way out there where you
它会在你身边的地方出现
can tell you like a stratosphere yes but
可以告诉你像平流层一样但是
yes I think about and we've had this
是的， 我想到了，我们已经 有了这个
discussion before I believe but think
我相信之前的讨论， 但想一想
about areas that are ravaged by some
关于被一些人蹂躏的地区
kind of
的种类
real disaster right well I thought where
真正的灾难， 我想到了哪里
infrastructure goes down as all of a
基础设施随着时间的推移而下降
sudden now our cell phones and our
突然现在我们的手机和我们的手机
internet no longer works where we are so
互联网不再适用于我们所在的地方
we can put these up and if it only takes
如果只需要，我们可以把它们放好
eight or ten of these balloons and all
八个或十个这些气球和所有
of a sudden infrastructure is at least
突然的基础设施至少是
in some way shape or form back exactly
在某种程度上形状或形式完全回归
like emergency calls can go out
像紧急电话可以出去
communications restored very cool okay
通讯恢复很酷很好
thanks for watching the category 5 TV
感谢收看5类电视
news room don't forget to Like and
新闻室不要忘记喜欢和
subscribe for all your tech news with a
订阅所有科技新闻
slight Linux bias and for more free
轻微的Linux偏见和更多 免费
content be sure to check out our website
内容一定要看看我们的网站
from the category 5 TV news room
来自5类电视新闻室
ambassador me
我是大使
[Music]
[音乐]